{
    "subject": "resource/Ray_Musto",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Raphael Musto",
    "human_readable": "The name of Ray Musto is Raphael Musto.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9743761420249939,
            "question": "Is Raphael Musto a different name for Ray Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9551628828048706,
            "question": "Is 'Raphael Musto' an alias for Ray Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8881108164787292,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Ray Musto and Raphael Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.854712963104248,
            "question": "Who is Raphael Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8432912826538086,
            "question": "What is the given name of Ray Musto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7744632363319397,
            "question": "What is Ray Musto's real name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7352806329727173,
            "question": "If someone called Ray Musto, what would their full name be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7348275780677795,
            "question": "Does Ray Musto use a different name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6359035968780518,
            "question": "How can Ray Musto be addressed using his full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6079906821250916,
            "question": "What is another way to refer to Ray Musto?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Ray Musto is Raphael Musto.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5506_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can Ray Musto be addressed using his full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5506_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Ray Musto use a different name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5506_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone called Ray Musto, what would their full name be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5506_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5506_3.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents refer to an individual named \"Raphael Musto\" or sometimes referred to as \"Ray Musto\". Therefore, the statement that \"The name of Ray Musto is Raphael Musto\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}